# This is all the question data, and was generated from the website, opentdb.com

question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 'Shrek' film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Tiananmen Square protests of 1989 were held in Hong Kong.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The very first recorded computer 'bug' was a moth found inside a Harvard Mark II computer.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Chevrolet Corvette has always been made exclusively with V8 engines only.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Gadgets", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The communication protocol NFC stands for Near-Field Control.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The card game 'Munchkin' won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The anime Attack on Titan was directed by Tetsur Araki, the same person who directed the anime"
                 " Highschool of the Dead.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 'Toaru Kagaku no Railgun' anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their"
                 " abilities.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injured, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In 'Star Trek', Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon"
                 " lineage.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible"
                 " universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube's ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Celebrities", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "Lady Gaga's real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Wilt Chamberlain scored his infamous 100-point-game against the New York Knicks in 1962.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In 'Call Of Duty: World At War', the first appearance of the 'PPSH-41' in 'Zombies' was in the"
                 " map 'Der Riese'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Linus Sebastian is the creator of the Linux kernel, which went on to be used in Linux, Android,"
                 " and Chrome OS.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'Green Eggs and Ham' consists of only 50 different words.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
